Please, Man of God, help me! I cannot walk due to a fractured femur.
For one year now, I cannot do anything on my own.
I cannot walk; I cannot go to my workplace.
I cannot even take a bath without the help of my wife.
Please, Man of God, help me!
Healing In Jesus' Name
Stand up. Don't run, walk gently.
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus; I'm free!
Thank You, Jesus; I can walk now!
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Joshua Sunday Oladele.
The lady beside me is my beautiful wife.
What brought me to The SCOAN was a fracture of the femur.
It happened in 2014.
To the glory of God, I came here in 2015, met the man of God who laid hands on me and prayed for me.
I stood up and since then, I began to walk.
Before coming to The SCOAN, I had tried many places.
The very first day the accident happened, I was taken to the hospital.
I also went to a herbalist and stayed at his place for three months.
After three months, he asked me to go and buy crutches to be using for walking. I would be okay.
I bought the crutches, and I left that place.
When I got home, I realised that the bone was not joined.
So I went to another herbalist.
In fact, I tried so many herbalists.
At the end of the day, we realised that this situation was not ordinary.
We started moving from church to church for deliverance.
Still, there was no solution.
God finally directed me to The SCOAN.
I was opportune to meet the man of God.
Immediately he touched me, I stood up and walked.
Before, I could not go to my working place.
I even lost my job during the period I had the problem
because the accident did not happen during working hours,
When they expected me to return to work in time and they saw that I could not resume back to my duty,
they sent my payoff to me.
It was very difficult to feed because I was the breadwinner of the family.
I could not go to work.
My wife was the one taking care of me.
I couldn't even take my bath or go to the toilet by myself.
In fact, it was very difficult.
But after the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua, you are able to do all those things you could not do then.
After the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua, for the very first time, I stood up and walked without crutches.
Ok, there is one thing we want to ask you.
What was happening to you when the man of God was praying for you because we saw your leg moving?
Tell us - what were you feeling then as the man of God was praying for you?
When man of God tapped my leg, I felt heat.
When he asked me to stand up, I felt as if something fell down from my leg.
I felt a ring, something - I sensed that something dropped from my leg.
He then asked me to move.
That was how I began to walk.
Let's put our hands together for the miracle working Jesus!
With what the Lord has done in your life, setting you free from that problem,
what word of advice do you have for people listening to you all around the world?
My word of advice to viewers all around the world and everybody watching me right now is that
we should have faith in God.
Just as the man of God always says, when you have a problem, you should come to God,
don't run away from God.
In my case, it was when I came to The SCOAN that I received my healing without paying a penny or naira.
At the other places that I went to before, I spent a lot of money - some would charge me 50,000 naira,
at the very first place they charged me 80,000 naira, the second 50,000 naira, some 40,000 naira.
So what you are telling us is that when you came to The SCOAN, and God used Prophet T.B. Joshua
to pray for you in the name of Jesus Christ and you were set you free, no money was collected from you?
No money was collected from me. It was free of charge.
Let's put our hands together for the Lord Jesus Christ.
Let's hear from your wife.
Emmanuel!
(God with Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Temitope Oladele. The man standing beside me is my husband.
I thank God today because I'm very happy.
When we came here two years ago and met Prophet T.B. Joshua here,
he prayed for my husband and my husband walked instantly.
I am very happy.
It wasn't easy because I was the only one helping him
and taking care of the children as well as providing food. It was me that was doing everything.
- But after the prayer and he was set free, he can do everything on his own.
- Yes.
- And you are very happy about that.
We thank God Almighty for what the Lord has done in your life.
Can you just exercise your body and let the people see what the Lord has done for you -
those things you could not do then.
Then I couldn't stand and walk like this.
But now, I can stand on this leg, I can move and run.
Glory be to God in the highest.